

□ (+60) 14-881-7836 | ■ barlowy@protonmail.com | 回 gohanko | 回 gohanko

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary

Building software for the web — experienced in the Javascript ecosystem, currently writing API specs for payment systems.

Skills_

Languages Javascript, Python

Tooling Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn, ... various other JS libaries

Frameworks React, Hapi, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy

Industry Knowledge CI/CD, Agile Software Development

Work Experience _____

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

BACKEND DEVELOPER Apr. 2020 - Present

• Building an API that directly perform operations on databases using Hapi and MSSql.

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER Dec. 2018 - Apr. 2020

- Learned the Javascript/Frontend ecosystem without prior experience or exposure.
- · Worked in a team and inter-department environment to deliver thorough and detailed work without cutting corners.
- Built and maintained large and complex code bases used by millions of people.
- · Translate design and wire frames into code.
- · Maintained our legacy projects by squashing bugs, resolving security issues and perform required amendments to it.
- Participated in scrum related activities to ensure proper software development lifecycle.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018

• Implemented RESTful API server for a invoice tracking system.

- Collaborated with remote teams to deliver the product.
- Helped to implement a redesign on a social media management service.
- Built a shopify shop for a local car rental.

Education

Freelance

Riam Road Secondary School

Miri, Malaysia

Remote

MALAYSIAN CERTIFICATE OF EXAMINATION

Jan. 2014 - Dec. 2016

Cyberjaya, Malaysia

Cyberjaya, Malaysia

- The Malaysian Certificate of Examination is the equivalent of the GCSE in England or GCE Ordinary Level in the Commonwealth of Nations.
- · Scored a 3A 4B in the examination which includes Mathematics (A-), Science (A), English (A), Malay (B+), Moral Studies (B+), History (B), and Art (B+).
- The English subject has 2 results, one is the MCE result and the other is the GCE Ordinary Level result, in which I scored an A as well.

BRANDON YII · RÉSUMÉ JUNE 3, 2020